Dallas Bohanan

Help Desk/ Support Specialist

Auburn, WA 98092 dallasbohanan@icloud.com +1 253 397 7018

I'm pursuing a Help Desk role in an IT Department. I'm best defined as a hard-working passionate person who loves to learn and takes pride in his work. Base level knowledge in managing admin applications and solving technical problems. My most recent experience comes from 3+ years of Lobby officer duties where I handled and troubleshot many different devices like Printers, laptops, and different software, while also training an entire team on procedures of how to properly use software/applications and devices. I would love the opportunity to provide my skills to the Muckleshoot IT team and improve my knowledge.

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

Work Experience

Security Supervisor

Allied Universal - Bellevue, WA December 2018 to Present

I've worked in security for three years at a company called GM Cruise. This experience has developed a lot of skills that I now possess like leadership skills, following protocol, completing tasks, being vigilant about my work as well as managing my time, and the ability to work well in a team. while working here I improved my critical thinking skills and also learned to work with different devices through the art of troubleshooting.

Security Officer

US Security Associate - Seattle, WA December 2016 to December 2018

Started my Security Career here and worked here for just under 2 years. This is where I gained experience in the security field and learned the importance of work ethic, customer service, and job performance. My performance here allowed me to move to a better position and take valuable skills with me.

Education

Some College in Computer Science

Highline Community College - Des Moines, WA September 2017 to April 2019

High school diploma in General Studies

Kent-Meridian High School - Kent, WA September 2012 to June 2015

Skills

- Customer service (5 years)
- Time management (5 years)
- Work Ethic (5 years)
- Listening skills (5 years)
- Critical Thinking/Problem Solving (5 years)
- Lennel Applications (2 years)
- Minor Admin skills (2 years)

Additional Information

I also have additional skills in programming/ web development. The most notable languages that I have skills in are Python, javascript, CSS, HTML5, Git, and PowerShell commands.